engvid.com 2019-03-27

# Privacy Policy · engVid

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at langvid AT langvid DOT com.

At www.engvid.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by www.engvid.com and how it is used.

We enforce the use of https encrypted connections between your browser and our servers, to protect the privacy of all data transferred between you and us.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.engvid.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.engvid.com uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize page content based on visitors' browser type, or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at www.aboutads.info and Networking Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.

We also use third party advertisements. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as, but not limited to, cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and other technical information. This information is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York ESL school ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing teaching ads to someone who frequents teaching sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. engVid.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. engVid.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

You can opt-out completely of tracking by not visiting this website. You may request removal from our logs by emailing us with your IP address and the date(s) of your visit to our website.>
